So California, just so I understand, y'all have folks on here telling you to vote for a billionaire
instead of telling the billionaire to endorse the socialists?
This is what I'll be talking about.
But y'all don't be wanting to hear me because the Democrats in California literally just voted against health care for all.
The black Democrats, I think it was a couple of years ago, maybe one or two years, because what is time?
And they voted against reparations.
And there was a whole committee that had been meeting for time, put in time to come up with a reparations package.
And it was the blacks that sent it back.
And now I see folks on here telling y'all, I know this guy is a billionaire, but he's good.
He's much better than that other guy.
I don't get it.